One Dream,
oh.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for watching.
Oh, what's the top?
You should go Stussy elsewhere.
You are aware of who controls
this country, I presume.
It looked like I'd give a crap.
It's Kaido, right?
Tell him we're here!
To take down an emperor!
Dial it back, Luffy.
Kin'emon said we're supposed to lay low.
Oh, I was just kidding!
Sorry!
Let's see what the cards have to say about
the probability of you
surviving a month here.
A firm 19%.
Hmm.
That's an interesting sword you got there.
Where the heck did you get that thing?
It's a Fancy Pants Famous one, right?
Well, if it is what I think
it is, it's a powerful one.
You should probably let me hold on to it.
No way.
You don't even know how to use it.
Now hand it over, come on.
I'ma slash them up good. Killed them.
Let's see what this thing can do!
Don't throw the scabbard, Luffy!
Now come go!
Pistol!
You're not using it right!
Even the lizard's biting me!
Hey, knock it off!
Straw sword.
His sword's creepy.
I feel bad for the lizard.
That was awesome!
Impressive.
Why is he still standing?
Observe.
That's minus one life.
You seem confused.
These straw men each represent
the lives of my subordinates.
With my straw straw powers, I can
infuse my body with their spirits.
They take damage for me.
If I amass ten souls, I can die ten times.
Now, let's play a game, shall we?
A game?
Here.
We'll let my straw man cards decide.
Let's go.
I'm not so bold as to challenge two
members of the worst generation at once.
At least not in a fair fight, that is.
He's a bigger pain in
the ass than he looks.
I should have expected it.
Now let us begin.
The Fool, reversed.
Drat, this card represents
internal discord.
A shame i'll try to draw
a better card next time
despite the risk of a
bad draw there are cards!
Included that expand one's ability
well beyond its natural limits?
Tom, you gotta hang in there.
She feels really hot.
That must be why her dog is freaking out.
You cowards!
You're not getting away!
Hey, Captain, I think
they're getting away!
I've drawn a good one.
The Hierophant reversed
the card of pursuit.
Hey, Lupi, watch over the brat.
Be right back.
Won't take long.
I'll handle it.
That's it!
The hell?
Two-sword style.
Nigiri.
Tower climb!
Ripple!
Shouldn't we go after them, sir?
The Hierophant.
It's a card of guidance.
In other words, a wise figure
will lead them to safety.
What a pain in my ass!
So, what's the status on the brat, Luffy?
Yow!
Tama's really burning up!
Hey, doggie! Hurry!
Hey, why'd you stop?
Are you kidding me?
Did you get us lost?
We don't have a lot of time to waste.
Make up your mind.
You want to try right?
I advise left.
You brave samurai are simply
teeming with strength.
Where'd you come from?
It's no easy feat to drive off Hawkins
Who are you?
The woman you saved earlier?
I owe you my thanks, Green One!
You may call me Tsuru.
Hmm?
What the hell?
You were hiding in that
dog's tail the whole time?
It's true.
My gratitude knows no bounds, good sir.
Take this.
Wipe her brow and make that
poor child more comfortable.
Thanks!
I hope this doesn't sound too forward.
However, if it's all right, I insist
that you leave Otama in my care.
You know Otama?
Indeed.
Gotcha.
That'd be great.
You see, she drank dirty river water.
All because she was hungry
and it really messed her up.
Forget the doctor in that case.
We should take her to
my tea house instead.
Tea?
What in the hell are you thinking, lady?
We don't have time for
tea when she's dying.
I don't even know this pipsqueak, but
it's clear that she's in bad shape.
You're right.
But the best remedy to
counteract the river's poison
is a special tea and herb
blends that we carry.
Heed my advice, and she'll
be better in no time.
Okay, then.
I think we should do it.
Thanks a lot.
I still owe you a favor.
I would like to tend to your
injuries, if I may, sir.
For you, sir.
Ah, sweet Tang dumplings.
Nothing I love better from this tea house.
I don't get to eat these as much anymore.
It keeps me going, though.
You say that in jest.
But before you know it, you'll be eating
as many as you wish, just like old times.
Here's hoping.
Hey, geyser!
Time for you to pack
it up! They're closing!
No, Kiku dear, you can't pay
the street tax, right, Pear?
I've told you before, I'm
willing to help you with that.
And all you have to do is marry me.
You'd never have to work again.
Plus, you can help yourself to all
the fresh food from the farm, P.
I promise I'll make you a happy woman.
But I'm far below your social standing.
If you're not ordering anything,
then I ask that you leave.
You think I would order anything
from this place? Come on!
Eating dumplings made from scraps?
What in places do you take me for?
I would never stoop so low.
It would be an embarrassment, Peef.
Did you forget that I'm a
famous Yokozuna at the capital?
I'm the greatest sumo
wrestler in the land of Wano!
Urashima!
Quit the tea house and come with me!
I can take you far away from
this poverty-stricken lifestyle!
No more selling leftovers to get by.
Think of how good you'll have it.
Okiku!
Otsuru!
Otama drank the river water and fell ill.
My goodness.
Please, lady.
You gotta do something.
Okiku.
Brew the evil purging herbs.
Yes, right away.
Hey!
Just who do you think you guys are?
Hey, big boy, move it.
Shut your trap!
I don't have to move for anyone!
Okiku, I'll have a wrestling
match in Bekori Town today, Pei.
I hope you'll come so I can
show you just how strong I am.
Did we find them?
It looked like the Straw Hats.
Maybe I should go and talk to
them before there's any trouble.
I don't know, Beppo.
Nothing personal, but
you kind of stick out.
Better luck next time, pal.
Well, we should probably report
this to the captain for now.